face-pic.com 2008-12-17

# face-pic.com - Privacy Policy

Help > Privacy & Opt-In Policy

To register with face-pic.com, you are required to read the following Privacy & Opt-In Policy . 

Face-pic.com is committed to protecting the privacy of its members. This statement explains how we collect information from you and what we do with it.

**INFORMATION REQUESTS**

 ** **  
face-pic.com offers a variety of online resources. In order for you to make full use of the resources on our site, we ask you to provide some basic information. When you register as a face-pic member, you will be asked for your e-mail address. Some of our additional services, such as mobile picture messaging require you register your mobile phone number with us.

**PROMOTIONS**

 ** **  
Unless you select to Opt-In, we will NOT use your face-pic.com registration information to send you promotional materials that we think may interest you. You will only receive promotional emails on behalf of advertising partners if you elect to Opt-IN for such promotional materials. Please note that Opt-in email will always come to you from face-pic on behalf of the advertiser or sponsor, never from the advertiser or sponsor directly.

We do not transfer user names, e-mail addresses or registration information to any business partner, advertiser, sponsor, or outside organization unless you opt-in to a specific promotion that requires us to share your information.

  **CHOICE/OPT-OUT**

 ** **  
Our members are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for their registration information. Members can also opt in or out at any time by changing their personal account settings. If you received a promotion from us, it is because you have given permission for us to send you an email.  

**HOW DO I GET REMOVED FROM YOUR EMAIL LIST**

** **  
If you wish to unsubscribe follow the instructions at the bottom of any email, or log in to your account, click on Options then Change Settings. If you have received an unwanted email sent by face-pic.com please forward a copy of the email with your comments to help@face-pic.com

**YOUR MOBILE INFORMATION**

 ** **  
We will only send promotional information to your mobile if you have selected to Opt-In when registering with us.  
You can opt-out at anytime by changing your account settings or emailing us at help@face-pic.com  

**COOKIES**

** **  
Cookies are small text files that most Web sites, including face-pic.com, place on your computer. Cookies help us identify you. Cookies delivered to you through banner ads are collected by our advertisers. We don't have access to any specific information they may provide. Those serving banner ads on our site only provide us with information in aggregate form. No individual information is given to us. face-pic.com is not able, and does not wish, to use cookies to track your activities on the Web outside of our site. No cookie delivered by us will interfere with the operation of your computer.  

**SHARED INFORMATION**

** **  
Face-pic.com does not provide personal individual information about you to others. Face-pic will not under any circumstance share your personal information with a business partner, advertiser or other organization. We do, however, caution users about electing to provide their personal information to face-pic partners once users have linked to a partner site from a face-pic email or banner. You should review the privacy policies of these partner sites in order to confirm the way in which they handle their users' information. Face-pic.com may share numerical demographic information gathered from its users, in aggregate form, with others such as advertisers or sponsors. No personal/individual information is provided to advertisers or sponsors.  

**GENERAL CONSIDERATIONS**

** **  
Face-pic.com cannot guarantee that the information you provide to us is completely safe, although we are careful to try to prevent problems. There may be technical problems beyond our control that may make it accessible to unauthorized persons.

If face-pic.com is acquired, our user information may be among the assets transferred to the buyer in the sale. Internet-based commerce is dynamic and changing. We may change our privacy policy in the future in order to adjust to these changes. We recommend that you check it frequently.

As a member, you also have the choice to Opt-out at any time, and for any reason. Email email sent to you by face-pic will always provide information on how to opt-out from the list. Once you opt-out, your data will no long receive promotional emails or SMS text messages from us.

**PROTECT YOURSELF**

** **  
Never give out personal information such as your address, phone number or banking details to strangers on the internet  
as we can not be responsible for any illegal or harmful actions that may result.  
We will never write to you and ask you for your face-pic password, never give it out to anyone.  

**REMOVING YOUR INFORMATION**

** **  
You can delete your account at anytime to remove all your information, or ask us to do it for you by sending an email to help@face-pic.com. After deleting your account we may still have information on you stored in our backups and archives for some time, but this information will never be used, shared or sold.  

**EXTERNAL LINKS**

This site contains links to other sites. Face-pic is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

By registering with face-pic.com, you agree to be bound by the terms & conditions of this Privacy & Opt-In policy.

If you have questions or comments on this Privacy & Opt-In Policy, please email us at help@face-pic.com

face-pic.com Limited is a registered business in England. Registration Number 4490231
